{"data":[{"question":"I didn't see Nancy since she moved to London.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"didn't see","b":"since","c":"moved","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"- Didn't see-> haven't seen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Jane gave up to smoke because she wanted to save money.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"gave up","b":"to smoke","c":"because","d":"to save","answer":"2","explain":"- To smoke-> smoking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"I came here so as to I could see you.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"came","b":"so as to","c":"could","d":"you","answer":"2","explain":"- So as to-> so that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"In my opinion that girl is enough beautiful to be a movie star.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In my opinion","b":"enough","c":"to be","d":"star","answer":"2","explain":"- Enough beautiful-> beautiful enough","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"I picked up the vase carefully so as to not break it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"picked up","b":"carefully","c":"not","d":"it","answer":"3","explain":"- Not-> so as not to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"We put up a fence to prevent the rabbit to escape.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"put up","b":"fence","c":"to prevent","d":"to escape","answer":"4","explain":"- To escape-> from escaping","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"They no longer didn't smoke cigarettes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"no longer","b":"didn't","c":"smoke","d":"cigarettes","answer":"2","explain":"- Didn't -> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"He seldom come to class late.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"seldom","b":"come","c":"to","d":"late","answer":"2","explain":"- Come-> comes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"She no longer wastes time to chatter with her friends.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"no longer","b":"wastes","c":"to chatter","d":"with","answer":"3","explain":"- To chatter-> chatting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"She has gone in a diet so that she will lose weight.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has gone","b":"in","c":"so that","d":"will lose","answer":"2","explain":"- In-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"}]}